<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>windshield replacement &#8211; Auto Glass Mart San Diego</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/windshield-replacement/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Windshield Replacement Experts</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 19:27:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/cropped-AGM-Logo-thumbnail-32x32.png</url>
	<title>windshield replacement  - Auto Glass Mart San Diego</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>When to complete windshield replacement</title>
		<link>/windshield-replacement/when-to-complete-windshield-replacement/</link>
					<comments>/windshield-replacement/when-to-complete-windshield-replacement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Auto Glass]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 19:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[windshield replacement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=327</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When to complete a windshield replacement DON&#8217;T WAIT TO REPLACE! A damaged windshield is much more of a hazard than simply being an eye sore.  Airbags are designed to deflect off the windshield.  If your auto glass fails or pops out due to improper installation, you lose that vital protection.  Also, an intact windshield is crucial to the &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/windshield-replacement/when-to-complete-windshield-replacement/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">When to complete windshield replacement</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><img loading="lazy" class="alignright size-medium wp-image-213" src="/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/AGM-Logo-300x95.png" alt="" width="300" height="95" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/AGM-Logo-300x95.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/09/AGM-Logo-768x243.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/09/AGM-Logo-1024x324.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2018/09/AGM-Logo.png 1226w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" />When to complete a windshield replacement</h1>
<p>DON&#8217;T WAIT TO REPLACE!</p>
<p>A damaged windshield is much more of a hazard than simply being an eye sore.  Airbags are designed to deflect off the windshield.  If your auto glass fails or pops out due to improper installation, you lose that vital protection.  Also, an intact windshield is crucial to the overall safety of your car structure. Generally providing around half of the support strength in a rollover accident! In many cases, such as the following, insurance companies insist on replacing a windshield rather than repairing it.</p>
<p>In addition to safety many states, including California have laws that dictate whether or not you must replace a damaged windshield.  In San Diego, the laws require that you can not drive with a damaged windshield that obstructs your view.  While of course, this is up to the discretion of the law enforcement personnel that inspects the windshield it is always best to replace your windshield or auto glass if you are not sure and want to avoid a costly citation.  To learn more about windshield laws in San Diego, CA visit this site. http://www.californiacarlaws.com/cracked-windshield/</p>
<p>You should replace your windshield if it has any of the following:</p>
<p>cracks or chips near the edge of the windshield<br />
cracks longer than a certain length, usually around 3 to 6 inches<br />
cracks that radiate in several directions<br />
more than 2 or 3 cracks or chips<br />
Even for-profit insurance companies recognize that it’s worth spending the money now to avoid the risk of future damage and injury as a result of a faulty windshield or auto glass!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/windshield-replacement/when-to-complete-windshield-replacement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Windshield Replacement in San Diego</title>
		<link>/windshield-replacement/windshield-replacement-in-san-diego/</link>
					<comments>/windshield-replacement/windshield-replacement-in-san-diego/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Auto Glass]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 19:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[windshield replacement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=227</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Windshield repair isn&#8217;t an issue you can ignore. In the event you go on driving using a damaged windshield, those cracks are likely to worsen. Eventually, your windshield can even end up shattering into pieces. You can find alternatives for windshield replacement San Diego County if you&#8217;re concerned about costs. Here&#8217;s where to see the &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/windshield-replacement/windshield-replacement-in-san-diego/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Windshield Replacement in San Diego</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Windshield repair isn&#8217;t an issue you can ignore. In the event you go on driving using a<br />
damaged windshield, those cracks are likely to worsen. Eventually, your windshield can<br />
even end up shattering into pieces. You can find alternatives for windshield replacement<br />
San Diego County if you&#8217;re concerned about costs. Here&#8217;s where to see the most cost-<br />
effective options available.</p>
<h3>Research Prices</h3>
<p>The San Diego Area is a large area, meaning consumers have lots of<br />
options. Do your research! You won&#8217;t find any company in San Diego that offers better<br />
service than San Diego Auto Glass Mart. We&#8217;re a knowledgeable and trustworthy group of<br />
experts set on getting you the best quality windshield replacement for the best price.<br />
You can call us or come in to get a quote or more information.</p>
<p>Should you get price quotes from lots of different companies, you&#8217;ll find that the most<br />
affordable options in the region are right here at San Diego Auto Glass Mart. You could<br />
have to call numerous companies only to realize that the best deals are right here. Your<br />
time is valuable. Let us help you today.</p>
<h3>Try To Have Your Windshield Repaired Instead</h3>
<p>You shouldn&#8217;t think that <a href="/windshield-replacement-san-diego/"><strong>windshield replacement</strong></a> is the only option you have. In the<br />
event the cracks in your windshield continue to be reasonably small, you could get the<br />
windshield repaired instead. This could save you some cash. However, often times<br />
windshield repairs fall short of getting the job done. You could end up with even more<br />
issues if you go for the quick fix. At our prices, you&#8217;ll find that it is well worth it<br />
to get your windshield replaced and have something brand new.</p>
<p>If you&#8217;re considering whether replacement is undoubtedly an option, it&#8217;s a brilliant<br />
idea to check out the dimensions of your cracks. When the cracks remain small compared<br />
to a dollar, fixing your windshield ought to be perfectly fine. Only larger cracks<br />
should require windshield replacement.</p>
<h3>Explore Financing Can Sometimes be an Option</h3>
<p>In the event you can&#8217;t afford <a href="/windshield-replacement-san-diego/">windshield replacement</a>, you must try to finance the<br />
expense of your brand-new windshield. A lot of companies offer financing options to<br />
their clients. Most of the time, the rates of interest for this type of financing is<br />
low, as well as the credit requirements aren&#8217;t too strict.</p>
<p>Should you finance your windshield, you won&#8217;t need to worry about what you are able to<br />
afford and what you can&#8217;t afford. You&#8217;ll just have the ability to give attention to<br />
getting this looked after. In a short time, you&#8217;ll have a completely new windshield, and<br />
you&#8217;ll have the opportunity to return to making use of your car just like you usually<br />
do.</p>
<p>Given that you&#8217;re aware of the most significant alternatives for <a href="/windshield-replacement-san-diego/">windshield replacement</a><br />
San Diego County, you can begin exploring a few of your choices. You should certainly<br />
try to obtain your windshield replacement at a lower price. Don&#8217;t let your finances stop<br />
you from handling your windshield! Your safety is always the most critical thing and<br />
indeed can&#8217;t be overrated. If you spend too long searching for options, you could end up<br />
creating an even bigger issue. Come down to our shop today to get your windshield<br />
replaced before things get worse. You&#8217;ll be relieved to have the problem solved.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/windshield-replacement/windshield-replacement-in-san-diego/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
